Guide to the Tobacco Collection, 1828-1987 and undated, bulk 1870-1955 RL.01300
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Tobacco collection
1828-1987, bulk 1870-1955
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
RL.01300
5 Linear Feet
The Tobacco Collection spans the years 1828-1987, with the bulk of the items dating from the late 19th and early 20th centuries, and contains material assembled by library staff related to the manufacturing, sale, and use of tobacco in the United States, particularly in the South. There are also items referring to tobacco cultivation and processing. Printed advertising predominates, but the contents also include items that are not paper products. Typical paper-based items include cigarette and cigar advertising trade cards of W. Duke, Sons & Co., Lorillard, Liggett and Myers, John Player and Sons, and various other American and British companies; tobacco advertisements by Krueger and Brown of N.Y.; and souvenir tobacco albums published by Allen & Ginter. Other forms of advertising in the collection include broadsides, pamphlets, books, leaflets, letters, envelopes, cigar and cigarette boxes and labels, cans, a plate, wrappers, labels, and catalogs. Images include birds, animals, battle scenes, and persons, including a series on "African Types." The bulk of the material dates from the later decades of the 19th century and the early 20th century but there are items dated earlier and later. The contents are primarily domestic, chiefly pertaining to business concerns in North Carolina and Virginia, but items from other countries are also included. Items are physically arranged by company name when known, otherwise by format. For easier searching, the descriptive finding aid is arranged in two alphabetical sections, by company name and by format.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Tobacco Collection is an artificial collection assembled from items acquired by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library from the 1930s to the present.
Collection Overview
The Tobacco Collection spans the years 1828-1987, with the bulk of the items dating from the late 19th and early 20th centuries, and contains material assembled by the library staff related to the manufacturing, sale, and use of tobacco in the United States, particularly in the South. There are also items concerning its cultivation and processing. Printed advertising predominates, but the contents also include artifacts and cloth items. Typical items include cigarette and cigar advertising trade cards of W. Duke, Sons & Co., Lorillard, Liggett and Myers, John Player and Sons, and various other American and British companies; tobacco advertisements by Krueger and Brown of N.Y.; and souvenir tobacco albums published by Allen & Ginter. There are also many posters, large and small, and printed materials, chiefly pamphlets and leaflets, some addressing tobacco farmers. The contents are primarily domestic, chiefly pertaining to business concerns in North Carolina and Virginia, but items from other countries are also included, and there are some items in the Spanish language.
The collection contains many advertising posters from the early years of American commercial color printing. Also present are cloth items: small silks, blankets, and rugs that were in use in the period around 1912 as both inserts and premiums. The various series of these cloth materials are listed in Jefferson R. Burdick's The American Card Catalog. Trade cards are present, chiefly in the W. Duke Sons & Co. Papers, as insert cards that were issued not only by the Dukes but also by their competitors. Card depict animals, flags, battle scenes, photographic views, and various persons, including a series on "African Types" from the 1930s. Other forms of advertising in the collection include broadsides, pamphlets, books, leaflets, letters, envelopes, cigar boxes and labels, cans, a plate, wrappers, labels, and catalogs. Pamphlets include an almanac, a smoking guide, a company history, and many other publicities related to tobacco cultivation and manufacturing. One 20th century item found in the collection is a plastic box for Camel cigarettes dated circa 1945-1949, typical of those distributed at Duke football games.
Collection Arrangement
The Tobacco Collection is an artificial collection assembled by the staff of the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library.
The collection guide is divided into listings by company, when known, and another listing by format. Forms can be quite varied and include: posters; trade cards; fabric inserts and premiums; trays; broadsides; pamphlets; leaflets; letters; booklets; cigar box labels; cigar boxes; labels; and cans. Trade cards are sometimes further described as mechanical, metamorphic, see-through, shape, unusual feature, postal, and insert.
Related Material
Tobacco advertisements collection, circa 1942-1969 (John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Avertising, and Marketing History)
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Great Britain -- Commerce -- History; Tobacco industry -- Great Britain -- History; Tobacco industry -- United States -- History; Pamphlets; Posters; Virginia -- Commerce -- History; United States -- Commerce -- History; North Carolina -- Commerce -- History; Advertising cards; Cigarette cases; Broadsides (notices); Cigarette cards; Cigar boxes; Africans in advertising; Cigarette industry -- History; Smoking -- United States; Tobacco -- Marketing; Advertising -- Cigarettes; Advertising -- Tobacco; Advertising -- Tobacco -- Pictorial works; W. Duke, Sons & Co.; P. Lorillard Company; R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Company; Krueger and Brown; Liggett & Myers Tobacco Company; John Player and Sons; American Tobacco Company; Allen & Ginter
- Listing of Items By Company Name
  Scope and Contents note
  Arranged by company name in alphabetical order.
  - "44" Cigar Company, 44 Cigars (Lipschutz) [Blotter] (Box 1)
  - A. Ralph & Co., Ralph's Carolina Snuff [Letter], 1870 Sept. 15 (Box 2)
    Philadelphia, Penna.
  - A. Ralph & Co., Ralph's Carolina Snuff [Insert] (Box 2)
  - A. Ralph & Co., Ralph's Carolina Snuff [Wrappers], 2 items (Box 2)
  - A. Ralph & Co., Snuff [Envelope], 1870 Oct. 8 (Box 2)
  - A.G. Howard & Co., Rabbit Foot Cigars [Trade Card], 2 items (Box 1)
    Atlanta, Ga.
  - A.J. Simonds, Allen's Jewel Plug [Trade Card] (Box 2)
    Brattlesborough, Vt.
  - Alexander Boguslavsky, Ltd., Turf (Conan Doyle Characters)[Insert Cards], 25 items (Box 1)
    London, Eng.
  - Alex'r Cameron & Co., Venus [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
    Va.
  - Allen and Ginter, American Indians [Poster] (Box 5)
  - Allen and Ginter, Birds of the Tropics [Poster] (Box 5)
  - Allen and Ginter, Editors [Poster] (Box 5)
  - Allen and Ginter, Pirates of the Spanish Main [Poster] (Box 5)
  - Allen and Ginter, Richmond Straight-Cut [Poster] (Box 5)
  - Allen and Ginter, Virginia Brights [Poster] (Box 5)
  - Allen and Ginter, World's Smokers [Poster] (Box 5)
  - Allen and Ginter, Birds of America, Snow Bird [Insert Cards] (Box 5)
  - Allen and Ginter, seven small printed albums of insert cards [Souvenir Albums] (Box 1, Acc. 10-31-1990)
  - American Cigar Co., Division of American Brands. Antonio y Cleopatra Grenadiers [Cigar Box] (Cigar-box 1-2)
    N.Y.
  - American Tobacco Company, Sovereign Cigarettes [Clipping] (Box 5)
    Enquirer Sun, Columbus, Ga., 1917
  - American Tobacco Company, Bull Durham [Poster], 6 items (Box 5)
  - American Tobacco Company, Bull Durham Gold Watch Fob (Box 5, Vault 1)
  - American Tobacco Company, Liberty Long Cut Tobacco [Wrappers], 7 items (Box 5)
  - American Tobacco Company, Mayos Cut Plug Wrappers [Wrappers], 2 items (Box 5)
  - American Tobacco Company, "111" Cigarettes [Wrappers], 4 items (Box 5)
    "111" Cigarettes, made between 1903 and 1950.
  - American Tobacco Company, U.S. Marine Cut Plug [Wrappers], 12 items (Box 5)
  - American Tobacco Company, Victory Wrappers [Wrappers], 27 items (Box 5)
  - American Tobacco Company, Herbert Tareyton Cigarettes [Trade Cards (Insert)], 27 items (Box 5)
  - American Tobacco Company, "The American Tobacco Story" [Booklet] (Box 5)
  - American Tobacco Company, Victory [Cigar Box Cover], 2 items (Box 6)
  - American Tobacco Company shingle, from the first factory built in Durham, 1865 (Box 8)
  - American Tobacco Company, Duke's Mixture Advertisements, 1902, 6 items (Oversize-box 52)
  - Baydex Cigarettes, "African Types," 1930s [Trade Cards], 24 cards (Box 1)
    [Acquired by the John Hope Franklin Research Center for African and African American History and Culture.]
  - Boehm, Bendheim & Co., Tobacco Commission Merchants [Trade Card] (Box 1)
    Savannah, Ga.
  - Boston Cigar & Tobacco Co., Poet Cigars (William Cullen Bryant) [Envelope] (Box 1)
    Boston, Mass.
  - British-American Tobacco Co., Ltd., Drummond's Horseshoe [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
    Petersburg, Va.
  - British-American Tobacco Co., Ltd., Cycle Cigarettes [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - British-American Tobacco Co., Ltd., Winner Plug Tobacco [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - Brown & Williamson, Old North State Cigarette [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - Brown & Williamson., Old North State Cigarette [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - Brown's Ware House, Moseley R.D. Brown's, Alpha-Beti-Cal Advertiser [Pamphlet], 1877 (Box 1)
    Winston, N.C.
  - Buchanan & Lyalls Mf'g., Planet & Neptune Plug Tobacco [Poster] (Box 6)
  - Click-Rierson Co., "Reference and Responsibility" [Leaflet] (Box 1)
  - Consolidated Cigar Corporation., Dutch Masters Perfecto [Cigar Box] (Cigar-box 1-2)
  - D.H. McAlpin Co., Chew Virginia Leaf [Poster] (Box 6)
  - D.S. Erb & Co., La Flor de Erb Cigar [Poster] (Box 1)
  - David Dunlop, Belle of Virginia [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - David Dunlop, Columbia [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - David Dunlop, The Derby [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - David Dunlop, Fair Maid [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - David Dunlop, La Plata [Poster], 2 items (Oversize-box 1)
  - E.V. Schnoor Cigar Co, Mapacuba Cigars [Envelope] (Box 2)
    Wichita, Kansas
  - EE-M Co., "EE-M Smoking Tobacco and Cigarettes" [Pamphlet], 1896 (Box 1)
  - F.R. Durgin, Flying Dude Cigar [Envelope] (Box 1)
    Brattleboro, Vt.
  - F.W. Felgner & Sons, Miners' Extra Smoking Tobacco [Wrappers], 3 items (Box 1)
    Baltimore, Md. (Successor to American Tobacco Company and F.H. Bischoff).
  - F.W. Felgner & Sons, Price List of Smoking Tobacco [Pamphlet], 1866 Aug. 1 (Box 1)
  - Fabrica de Tabacos, Cigar Box (Undesignated) [Labels] (Box 1)
    Havana, Cuba.
  - Fabrica de Tabacos, LaVencedora [Labels] (Box 1)
  - Fabrica de Tabacos, La Esprecion [Labels] (Box 1)
  - G.W. Gail & Ax of Baltimore, Navy Smoking Tobacco [Poster] (Oversize-folder 1)
    Baltimore, Md.
  - G.W. Gail & Ax of Baltimore, Navy [Wrappers], 5 items (Oversize-folder 1)
  - G.W. Gail & Ax of Baltimore, Navy Smoking Tobacco [Wrappers] (Oversize-folder 1)
  - Gebruder Blum, Auswalt billiger Sorten [Leaflet] (Box 1)
    Zigarettenfabrik, Goch, Rhineland.
  - Gonzalez & Sanchez, Havana Cigars [Booklet] (Box 1)
  - Goodwin & Co., Old Judge [Trade Card] (Box 1)
  - Hall & Daniel, Little Kate Chewing Tobacco [Trade Card] (Box 1)
    Hickory, N.C.
  - Harris & Flippen, Tobacco Barn Flues [Broadside], 1885 June (Box 1)
    Greensboro, N.C.
  - Harry Weissinger Tobacco Co., Peace & Good Will [Poster] (Box 6)
    Louisville, Ky.
  - Havatampa Cigar Co., Hav-a-Tampa [Cigar Box], 3 items (Cigar-box 1-2)
    Tampa, Fla.
  - Helmar (Turkish Tabacco), Turkish Cigarettes [Poster] (Box 6)
  - Hill & Fritz, Kangaroo Tobacco [Poster] (Box 1)
    St. Louis, MO.
  - Hill & Skinner, "To the Planters of Virginia and North Carolina" [Pamphlet], 1875 (Box 1)
    Richmond, Va.
  - Holmes & Miller Plug & Twist Tobacco, 189__ (Signed Laura) [Letter] (Box 1)
    Salisbury, N.C.
  - Holmes & Miller Plug & Twist Tobacco. ca. 189__ [Envelope] (Box 1)
  - Interstate Tobacco.- Person-Garrett Co.- Whitehead & Anderson, Inc., Border Belt Smoking Leaf Is Best [Broadside], 1947 April 15 (Box 1)
  - Interstate Tobacco.- Person-Garrett Co.- Whitehead & Anderson, Inc., Border Belt Smoking Leaf Is Best [Broadside], 1947 May 26 (Box 1)
  - Interstate Tobacco.- Person-Garrett Co.- Whitehead & Anderson, Inc., Border Belt Smoking Leaf Is Best [Broadside], 1947 June 23 (Box 1)
  - Interstate Tobacco.- Person-Garrett Co.- Whitehead & Anderson, Inc., Border Belt Smoking Leaf Is Best [Broadside], 1947 July 8 (Box 1)
  - J.H. McElwee, Ante-Bellum Smoking Tobacco [Label] (Box 1)
    Statesville, N.C.
  - J.W. Roberts & Son, Get Your Cigars Direct from "The Havana of America" [Leaflet] (Box 2)
  - J.W. Stoddard & Co., The Tiger, King of Rakes [Poster] (Box 2)
    Dayton, Ohio
  - Jacob G. Shirk, Homestead [Label] (Box 2)
    Lancaster, Penna.
  - Jamaica Tobacco Co. Ltd., Royal Jamaica [Cigar Band], 1981 (Box 1)
  - James G. Tinsley & Co., Fertilizers for Tobacco [Pamphlet], 1889 (Box 1)
  - John Player & Sons, Players Cigarettes [Insert Cards], 50 items (Box 1)
    London, England. (Gilbert & Sullivan Characters) First Series.
  - John Player & Sons, Players Cigarettes [Insert Cards], 50 items (Box 1)
    London, England. (Gilbert & Sullivan Characters) Second Series.
  - John Slater & Co., Smokers' Guide (For Men Only) "Slater's Stogies" [Booklet] (Box 2)
  - José Alonso y Ca., [Cigar Box Label] (Box 1)
  - Kinney Bros., Butterfly Collection [Poster] (Box 6)
  - Kinney Bros., Duel After the Ball [Poster] (Box 6)
  - Krueger & Brown, Author of Waverly [Cigar Box Label], 2 items (Box 1)
  - Krueger & Brown, Bella Primera [Cigar Box Label], 2 items (Box 1)
  - Krueger & Brown, Bonita Signora [Cigar Box Label] (Box 1)
  - Krueger & Brown, Royal Life [Cigar Box Label], 2 items (Box 1)
  - Krueger & Brown, Undesignated [Cigar Box Label], 4 items (Box 1)
  - Krueger & Brown, Author of Waverly [Cigar Wrapper] (Box 1)
  - Krueger & Brown, Bella Primera [Cigar Wrapper], 2 items (Box 1)
  - Krueger & Brown, Royal Life [Cigar Wrapper] (Box 1)
  - La Reclama Cuban Factory, La Reclama Examiner [Broadside] (Box 2)
    New York, N.Y.
  - La Reclama Cuban Factory, Smokers Guide [Booklet] (Box 2)
  - La Reclama Cuban Factory, La Reclama Cigar [Leaflet] (Box 2)
  - La Reclama Cuban Factory, La Reclama Cigar [Letter] (Box 2)
  - Lea & Noell, Leaf Tobacco [Broadslide ] (Box 1)
    Banner Warehouse, Danville, Va.
  - Lea & Noell, I am at Banner Warehouse Ed. M. Pace. [Trade Card] (Box 1)
  - Ledbetter & Co., Tom P. Ledbetter with Ledbetter & Co. [Trade Card] (Box 1)
  - Ligget & Myers, The New Tobaccoland USA [Pamphlet], 1948 (Oversize-box 1)
  - Ligget & Myers, Tobaccoland USA [Pamphlet], 1940, 2 items (Oversize-box 1)
  - Ligget & Myers, Tobaccoland USA [Pamphlet], 1951 (Oversize-box 1)
  - Liggett & Myers, Clipper Navy Plug [Trade Card] (Box 1)
  - Liggett & Myers, The Companies of Your Pleasure [Pamphlet], 1979 (Box 1)
  - Liggett & Myers, Catalogue of Presents Offered for Tobacco Tags Tobacco Coupons and Cigarette Coupons [Pamphlet], 1916 (Box 1)
  - Liggett & Myers, Fatima Cigarettes [Framed Picture] (Oversize-box 1)
  - Liggett & Myers, Bridge by Ely Culbertson, 1936 Play and Scoring [Pamphlet] (Box 1)
  - Liggett & Myers, Fatima Cigarettes [Framed Picture] (Oversize-box 1)
    NJ.
  - Liggett & Myers, Liggett Group, Tobaccoland Magazine [Pamphlet] (Oversize-box 1)
  - Liipfert, Scales & Co., School Boy & National Chew [Envelope], 1900 August 11 (Box 1)
  - Liipfert, Scales & Co., Save Liipfert, Scales & Co.'s Tags and Bags [Broadside], 1900 (Box 1)
  - Lone Jack Cigarette Co., Lone Jack Cigarettes [Plate] (Box 1)
    Lynchburg, Va.
  - M.V.B. Weighill, Rose Maccoboy, Rappee and Scotch, Railroad Snuff [Trade Card] (Box 2)
    Cincinnati, Ohio
  - Maclin-Zimmer-McGill, Just the Thing [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - Maclin-Zimmer-McGill, Lord Beaconsfield [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - Maclin-Zimmer-McGill, Picture of a King [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - Maclin-Zimmer-McGill, Red Funnel [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - Maclin-Zimmer-McGill, Sailor's Hope [Poster], 2 items (Oversize-box 1)
  - Maclin-Zimmer-McGill, Hard A Port Cut Plug [Playing Card] (Oversize-box 1)
  - Manuel Garcia Alonso, Undesignated [Cigar Box Label] (Box 1)
  - Moss, Birdsong & Co., Farmers Warehouse [Broadside] (Box 1)
  - Nat Sherman (tobacconist), Sherman's [Catalog ] (Box 2)
  - National Cigar Co., Private Label Cigars [Book ] (Box 1)
  - National Tobacco Works, Piper Heidseck Plug Tobacco [Poster] (Box 5)
  - National Tobacco Works, Newsboy Plug Tobacco [Poster] (Box 7)
  - New York & Havana Cigar Co., "Descriptive Price List" [Leaflet] (Box 1)
  - New York Cigar, Specimens of Cigar Box Labels [Book] (Box 1)
  - P.H. Mayo & Brother, Inc., Eglantine & Ivy [Trade Card] (Box 1)
  - Pace's (Brick) Warehouse, [Envelopes], 1883 March 8 and n.d., 2 items (Box 1)
    Winston-Salem, N.C.
  - Pace's (Brick) Warehouse, Pace's (Brick) Warehouse [Broadside] (Box 1)
  - Pace's (Brick) Warehouse, "Steer for Pace's Warehouse" [Brochure], 1882 (Box 1)
  - Pace's (Brick) Warehouse, Signed A.B.G. [Letter], 1883 March 8 (Box 1)
  - Parriah & Blackwell, Want… [Trade Card] (Box 1)
    Durham, N.C.
  - R.A. Patterson & Co., 6th Annual Descriptive Catalogue [Catalog], 1885 (Box 1)
  - R.F. Morris & Son M'f'g. Co., Ladies Choice & North State Mills Scotch Snuff & Smoking Tobaccos [Trade Bill & Letter], 1897 July 1 (Box 1)
  - R.F. Morris & Son M'f'g. Co., "Our Key Unlocks the Door"! [Broadside] (Box 1)
    Durham, N.C. (Key West Cheroots).
  - R.J. Reynolds, [Financial Statements], 1920, 1927-1932, 7 items (Box 2)
  - R.J. Reynolds, [Annual Report], 1961 (Box 2)
  - R.J. Reynolds, Whitaker Park [Brochure ] (Box 2)
  - R.J. Reynolds, Research [Pamphlet], 1960 (Box 2)
  - R.J. Reynolds, A Short History of R.J. Reynolds Tobacco Company [Pamphlet], 1961 (Box 2)
  - R.L. Swain Tobacco Co., Pinehurst Cigarettes [Label] (Box 2)
    Danville, Va.
  - Roth, Brunner & Feist, Old Glory & War Eagle Cheroots [Broadside] (Box 2)
    Cincinnati, Ohio (L. Richardson Drug Co., Greensboro NC).
  - S. Anargyrus, Egyptian Deities [Poster] (Box 7)
  - S. Anargyrus, Turkish Trophies [Insert Cards], 24 items (Box 7)
    24 of set of 25.
  - S.W. Travers & Co., A Few Facts on the Cultivation of Tobacco [Pamphlet], 1886 (Box 2)
  - Schulte Cigar Co, [Coupons], 4 items (Box 2)
  - Simpson & Smith, The "Gem Segar Pipe" [Broadside] (Box 2)
  - Southern Fertilizing Co., The Position Tobacco Has Held as the Chief Source of Wealth to Virginia [Pamphlet], 1876 (Box 2)
  - T.C. Williams Co., Dash [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - T.C. Williams Co., Diadem of Old Virginia [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - T.C. Williams Co., Golden Eagle [Poster], 2 items (Oversize-box 1)
  - T.C. Williams Co., Juno [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - T.C. Williams Co., Lucy Hinton [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - T.C. Williams Co., Nosegay [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - T.C. Williams Co., Victory [Poster] (Oversize-box 1)
  - T.C. Williams Co., Welcome Nugget [Poster], 2 items (Oversize-box 1)
  - T.E. Brooks & Co., El-Rees-So [Cigar Box] (Cigar-box 1-2)
    Red Lion, Pa.
  - The Geo. W. Helme Company, Helme's Railroad Snuff [Trade Card] (Box 1)
    Helmetta, N.J.
  - The Mammoth Tobacco Co., Notice "Winston's Best" Tobacco [Broadside] (Box 1)
  - The Watson Warehouse, Watson Warehouse [Trade Card] (Box 2)
    Wilson, N.C.
  - Toro y Compania, Sociedad en Comandita, El Toro de la Selva Tabacos [Cigar Box Label] (Box 2)
    San Juan, Puerto Rico.
  - Unknown, Various British companies [Album: insert cards], 188 cards (Box 2)
  - Unknown, New Size, New Kind [Booklet: cigarette papers] (Box 2)
    Anti-smoking reasons on each page.
  - Unknown, All About Cigarette Cards [Book: Cruse, Alfred J.] (Box 2)
    London.
  - Unknown, Cigarros Exquisitos [Cigar Box Labels], 3 items (Box 2)
  - Unknown, Habana [Cigar Box Labels] (Box 2)
  - Unknown, Undesignated Brand [Cigar Box Labels], 4 items (Box 2)
  - Unknown, Kohler's Handmade [Cigar Box Labels], 4 items (Box 2)
  - Unknown, Dick Custer [Cigar Box Labels], 2 items (Box 2)
  - Unknown, "La Decouverte des Cigars" [Clippings: Le Figaro] (Box 6)
  - Unknown, U.S. Naval Academy [Fabric Inserts: Athletes & college seals series] (Box 3)
    Annapolis--Rowing.
  - Unknown, Brown--Baseball [Fabric Inserts: Athlete & college seals series] (Box 3)
  - Unknown, Columbia--Hammer Throw, Hurdles, and Rowing [Fabric Inserts: Athletes & college seals series] (Box 3)
  - Unknown, Georgetown--Hockey and Hurdles [Fabric Inserts: Athletes & college seals series] (Box 3)
  - Unknown, Princeton--Hammer Throw and Hockey [Fabric Inserts: Athletes & college seals series] (Box 3)
  - Unknown, Stanford--Rowing [Fabric Inserts: Athletes & college seals series] (Box 3)
  - Unknown, Syracuse--Golf [Fabric Inserts: Athlete & college seals series] (Box 3)
  - Unknown, U.S. Military Academy [Fabric Inserts: Athletes & college seals series] (Box 3)
    West Point--Baseball, Golf, Rowing, and Track.
  - Unknown, Germany [Fabric Inserts: National flags, songs & flowers series] (Box 3)
    8 1/2" x 6 1/2."
  - Unknown, 13 Flags of America [Fabric Inserts (flannel): Flags of America] (Box 2)
    10 1/2" x 15 1/2."
  - Unknown, 6 Flags of America with Arms [Fabric Inserts (flannel): Flags of America] (Box 2)
    7 1/2" x 10 3/4."
  - Unknown, United States [Fabric Inserts (flannel): National flag with no emblem] (Box 2)
    8 1/2" x 12 1/2."
  - Unknown, No Brand Designation [Fabric Inserts (Plush, Fringed Ends): Rugs] (Box 3)
    3" x 5."
  - Unknown, No Brand Designation [Fabric Inserts (Plush, Fringed Ends): Rugs] (Box 3)
    2 1/2" x 4 1/2."
  - Unknown, Corea (Korea) [Fabric Inserts (flannel): National flags with decorated squares in corners, no emblems] (Box 3)
    5 1/4" x 8 1/4."
  - Unknown, Panama [Fabric Inserts (flannel): National flags with decorated squares in corners, no emblems] (Box 3)
  - Unknown, Turkey-Egypt [Fabric Inserts (flannel): National flags with decorated squares in corners, no emblems] (Box 3)
  - Unknown, Hayti [Fabric Inserts (flannel): National flags with corner emblems, no squares] (Box 3)
  - Unknown, Union Jack [Fabric Inserts (flannel): National flags with corner emblems, no squares] (Box 3)
    8 1/4" x 10 1/2."
  - Unknown, United States (Beige background) [Fabric Inserts (flannel): National flags with corner emblems, no squares] (Box 3)
  - Unknown, United States (Green background) [Fabric Inserts (flannel): National flags with corner emblems, no squares] (Box 3)
  - Unknown, No Brand Designation [Fabric Inserts (flannel): National flags, 21 items (Box 2)
  - Unknown, No Brand Designation [Fabric Inserts (flannel): National flags with emblem in squares in corners], 5 items (Box 3)
    5 1/2" x 8 1/4."
  - Unknown, No Brand Designation [Fabric Inserts (flannel): National flags with emblem in squares in corners], 14 items (Box 3)
  - Unknown, No Brand Designation [Fabric Inserts (flannel): National flags with emblem in squares in corners], 3 items (Box 3)
    8" x 11 1/2."
  - Unknown, No Brand Designation [Fabric Inserts: National flags series], 2 items (Box 3)
  - Unknown, No Brand Designation [Fabric Inserts (flannel): National flags], 3 items (Box 3)
    4" x 6 1/2."
  - Unknown, No Brand Designation [Fabric Inserts (flannel): National flags], 35 items (Box 2)
    5 1/4" x 8 1/2."
  - Unknown, No Brand Designation [Fabric Inserts (silks): College seals] (Box 3)
    University of N. Dakota.
  - Unknown, No Brand Designation [Fabric Inserts (silks): Military medal] (Box 3)